你已经等不及了要运行应用了吧  现在就让我们点击绿色的运行按钮
And now for the moment you've been waiting for, let's hit this green Run button.
然后会弹出选择运行设备的对话框  如果手头没有真机
It will prompt us to choose a device, without a physical device we
我们可以选择Android SDK自带的模拟器
can test the app using the emulator that comes with the Android SDK.
在配置Android Studio时
An Android virtual device should have already been created for
AVD(Android虚拟模拟器)应该已经自动创建完成了
you automatically when you set up Android Studio.
你只需要点击OK按钮即可
So you can go ahead and click OK.
利用模拟器启动起来的这段时间
While the emulator's booting up,
顺便说一下  如果你想修改你的模拟器
I want to point out that if you ever want to modify your emulator devices,
可以点击这个带有一个紫色设备和一个Android小人的按钮
you can click on this button with the purple device and the Android, and
打开AVD manager来管理你的Android虚拟设备
open up the AVD manager to manage your Android virtual devices.
它会列出已创建的设备
It lists out your existing devices, and
当然你也可以创建新的虚拟设备
you can always create another virtual device.
可以选择平台种类  设备型号
You can select the category of device and then a specific device.
和搭载的Android系统版本
Then you choose which platform version it should be running on.
可看到  目前这台电脑只下载了Lollipop版本的Android系统
And this is the only one that's available on this computer now.
选择Lollipop之后还应该选择Google API来创建Target
So Lollipop is good, and we choose the Google API's target, because it
可以使模拟器提前预装Google服务
will include some Google services already pre-installed on the emulator.
之后点击Next按钮
You can choose Next.
这里有很多选项和参数设置
There's a couple more options and settings that you can modify, for example,
比如你可能需要一个SD卡或者一个摄像头  都可以在这里选择
if you want an SD card, or a camera you can change those here, and
下一步点击Finish  就创建好了一个新的AVD了
then you can go ahead and click Finish, and it'll create a new AVD for you.